所以你总是说你睡不好，也不知道为什么，
So you say you don't sleep well and you don't know why
因为你感觉良好，平时也做了所有正确的事来获得一个像样的睡眠。
because you feel good and do all the right things in your life to get a decent night's sleep.
你所不知道的是，你实际上并没有做那些有助于
What you don't know is that you actually don't do the things that are conducive to
能迸发出快速眼动（深睡眠的最高形态）的坚实八小时的事情。
getting a solid eight hours with those needed spurts of rapid eye movement.
有些事情你甚至没有意识到会影响你进入深睡眠模式后
There are things you do that you are not even aware of that affect you getting
所必须的时间，而今天我们将告诉你哪里做错了。
the requisite hours in deep sleep mode, and today we are going to tell you what you're doing wrong.
首先，你并不孤单。
So first of all, you're not alone.
你知道吗，有研究称在美国高达60%的人
Did you know that in the USA it's reported that a whopping 60 percent of people
在大多数晚上甚至每晚都难以入睡？
have trouble sleeping most nights or even every night.
这是来自国家睡眠基金会（National Sleep Foundation）的说法，当涉及到睡眠时，
That's according to the National Sleep Foundation and when it comes to sleeping
这个组织是很有发言权的。
this organization knows what it's talking about.
同一项研究告诉我们，43%的人很少或者从来没有睡过好觉，
The same study tells us that 43 percent of those people rarely or never get a good night's sleep,
好吧，至少在13到64岁的人中。
well, at least people aged 13 to 64.
他们中的很多人说一晚连6个小时的睡眠都没有，
A lot of those folks say they don't even get six hours' sleep a night,
而坊间流传的说法是，如果我们想要感觉良好，应该睡7到9个小时。
and the word on the street is we should get seven to nine hours if we want to feel good.
睡眠剥夺的时代已经来临，而这里有一个重要的原因。
The sleep deprivation era is here, and there is one big reason why we seem to be sleeping less.
那就是科技，据国家睡眠基金会报道，
The reason is technology, with the National Sleep Foundation reporting that
95%的人会在睡前使用某种电子设备。
95 percent of people use an electronic gadget of some kind right before bed.
额... 你是不是就打算在睡觉前看这条视频？
Hmm, are you watching this show just before you intend to sleep?
然而我们说的不仅仅只有手机，还有电视也包含在这些设备列表中。
But we are not just talking about phones, TVs are included in the list of gadgets.
以下是一位专家在谈到睡前使用电子设备时所说的话，
This is what one expert said about gadget use before bed,
“从傍晚到入睡之间设备发出的人造光会抑制
“Artificial light exposure between dusk and the time we go to bed at night suppresses release of
促睡眠的褪黑激素的释放，并将昼夜节律推迟一小时，
the sleep-promoting hormone melatonin, enhances alertness and shifts circadian rhythms to a later hour,
使人更加难以入睡。”
making it more difficult to fall asleep.”
我们并不是说要抛弃掉电子设备，但如果你想快速入睡并且睡足8个小时，
We are not saying don't use gadgets, but perhaps if you want to get your eight hours and drift off quickly
你可能要考虑在睡前两个小时不浏览任何电子屏幕。
you might think about not looking at a screen for the two hours before you intend to sleep.
一项研究表明约有60％的人说他们在上床前使用笔记本或手机
Around 60 percent of people in one study said they use their laptop or phone right before they go to bed,
其中的一些人也会选择打电子游戏，
and some of them play computer games
这实际上不利于让自己感到疲惫并进入梦乡。
which is really not conducive to making yourself tired.
另一位睡眠专家是这样描述的：“在过去的50年里，我们已经看到
Another sleep expert said this about that, “Over the last 50 years, we've seen how
睡前观看电视已经成为一种常态，
television viewing has grown to be a near constant before bed,
而现在我们又看到新的信息技术，
and now we are seeing new information technologies
如笔记本电脑、手机、视频游戏和音乐设备，正迅速获得同样的地位。”
such as laptops, cell phones, video games and music devices rapidly gaining the same status.”
你可能认为这对你一点影响都没有，但根据专家的说法它确实有，
You might think it doesn't affect you at all, but according to those experts it does
而且有数据支持这个观点。
and there's data to back that up.
我们应该补充的是，关于人造光使人保持清醒的理论是有争议的，
We should add that the artificial light theory about keeping us awake is controversial
所以需要做更多的调查。
and so more research needs to be done.
研究显示，很多美国人在晚上不会静音手机，
According to studies a lot of Americans leave their phone alerts on during the night,
十分之一的受访者表示，手机有时会把他们吵醒。
and one in ten people interviewed said their phone woke them up during the night at times.
关闭提醒就好了，很简单的事情。
Just turn off the alerts, it's simple to do.
现在的问题是，很多人在网上有来自世界各地的朋友，
The problem these days is that many people have online friends all over the world,
于是当你在英国想睡觉的时候，你的美国朋友会在
so when you're trying to sleep in the UK your friends in the USA are sending you
微信上给你发喵星人的照片。
photos of kittens on Facebook Messenger.
可能你在亚洲有一个客户，当你想在加拿大睡觉的时候，
You might have a client in Asia who keeps posting stuff about work to you
他会不停地给你发一些工作上的消息。
when you're trying to sleep in Canada.
你无缘无故的惊醒，通常就是因为手机出现了状况。
You may wake up and not know why, but often it's because something went down in that phone of yours.
另一项研究表明，年轻人在这方面情况尤为严重，
Another study said younger folks were terrible at this,
72%的6到17岁的美国孩子睡觉时会带着手机。
saying that 72 percent of American kids aged six to seventeen go to bed with their phone.
在过去，孩子们可能会和一只毛毛熊或一本书睡在一起，这些东西不会发出任何声响。
In the past kids might have slept with a furry bear or a book, and those things don't make any noise.
为什么现在的人觉得他们在睡觉时需要带着手机?
Why do people these days feel they need to sleep with their phone?
有什么重要的内容以至于如此迫不及待？
What's so important that it can't wait?
真的对手机这么上瘾吗?
Are you really that addicted to the thing?
《赫芬顿邮报》(the Huffington Post)联合创始人安娜赫芬顿(Arianna Huffington)在采访中表示，
Co-founder of the Huffington Post, Arianna Huffington, has said in interviews
这种科技成瘾是一个重大问题，并且正在影响人们的心理健康。
that this tech addiction is a major issue and is affecting the mental health of people.
她说父母的情况同样糟糕，因此他们需要开始树立一个较好的榜样。
She said the parents are often as bad as the kids, so they need to start setting a better example.
她谈到科技产品给我们带来的多巴胺（传递兴奋），
She talks about the dopamine hits we get from technology,
因此睡前浏览朋友圈不是一个好主意。
and so scrolling through Facebook right before bed is not a good idea.
当她睡觉的时候，房间里没有任何科技设备。
When she sleeps there is no technology in her room at all.
睡前看社交媒体也会让你感到压力。
You might also get stressed by looking at social media before bedtime.
你真的不想在你试图入睡前得到一个“羡慕他人”的机会。
You really don't want to get a shot of envy right before you try and fall asleep.
“哦，瞧，我的一个朋友在我负担不起的某个国家的海滩上”
“Oh, look, there's my friend on beach in some country I can't afford to go to.”
在尝试入睡之前，这并不是你想看到的。
This is not what you want in your head before you try and fall asleep.
以上，即是科技让你睡不着觉的原因。
So, technology, this is what's keeping you awake.
我们的建议很简单。
Our advice is simple.
睡觉前至少两个小时不要看任何电子屏幕。
Do not look at any electronic screens at least two hours before bed time.
你可能不太相信，但这会对你的睡眠周期产生负面影响。
You might not believe it, but it's negatively affecting your sleep cycle.
如果你是父母，请不要在孩子的卧室里使用高科技。
If you're a parent, don't allow tech in your kids' bedrooms.
如果你是个孩子，放聪明点，把那些设备关掉。
If you're a kid, wise up and turn that stuff off.
表现出一定的自制力...
Show some self-control...
如果我们开始听起来像是在给你们上课，
and if we are starting to sound like we are giving you a lecture,
我们要说其实我们自己也才刚刚开始这么做。
we should say that we only just started doing this ourselves.
并且可以告诉你，我们的睡眠质量变好了。
We can tell you that we started to sleep better.
现在，假设你不使用电子产品，但仍然无法入睡。
Now let's say you don't use electronic gadgets but still can't sleep.
你没有感到沮丧或巨大压力，所以不知道问题出在哪里。
You are not depressed or particularly stressed and so don't know what the problem is.
你还没有坠入爱河，或者失去工作。
You haven't just fallen in love or lost a job.
你各方面很好，但睡觉对你来说很难。
You're fine, but sleeping is hard work for you.
你知道嘛，这有可能是因为你晚上喝的咖啡，或是喝的那些茶造成的。
You know, it could be those coffees you are having in the evening, or perhaps those cups of tea.
我们知道那些英国群众喜欢喝茶，他们中的很多人会在晚上来上一杯，
We know those British folks love their tea and quite a few of them will have a “cuppa”in the evening,
也许还会配上“晚餐”。
perhaps with their “supper”.
我们知道是因为我们亲眼目睹了。
We know this because we've seen it firsthand.
一杯上好的狄得利（tetley）红茶可能会让那些英国佬保持清醒。
That cup of the finest Tetley's tea could actually be keeping those Brits awake.
晚上7点喝的星巴克的卡布奇诺可能会毁掉一个美国佬的睡眠。
That cappuccino from Starbucks the American had at 7 pm could ruin that person's sleep.
下面是咖啡因的实情。
This is the lowdown on the drug caffeine.
一旦被咖啡因冲击后将在30到60分钟后达到巅峰。
Once you've had your hit you'll peak around 30 to 60 minutes later.
然后兴奋将趋于平稳，但是咖啡因的半衰期为5到6个小时，
That buzz will then plateau, but caffeine has a half-life of five to six hours,
这意味着你的身体需要5到6个小时才能摆脱一半的咖啡因。
meaning this is the time it takes for your body to get rid of half of the drug.
在那之后的几个小时内，你的体内仍然会有一些咖啡因。
You'll still have some caffeine in your system for hours after that.
现在，正如你所知的，这并不是说咖啡因可以和冰毒之类的
Now, as you know, it's not as if caffeine can be compared to a substance such as ice,
非法物质相比，但它是一种兴奋剂。
the illegal kind, but it is a stimulant.
我们也会承认美国人喜欢这些东西，就像那些英国人喜欢他们的茶一样。
And we should say that Americans love the stuff, perhaps just as much as those Brits love their tea.
我们发现的一项研究称：“美国成年人每天平均摄入的咖啡因
One study we found said this, “The average daily consumption of caffeine by adults in
约为每人300毫克。
the U.S. is about 300 mg per person.
这大约是世界平均水平的三倍。
This is about three times higher than the world average.
但这仍然只是重度饮茶国家的咖啡因消费量的一半
But it is still only half of the caffeine consumption in heavy tea-drinking countries
就比如英国和瑞典。”
such as England and Sweden.”
有些人太喜欢喝咖啡了，
Some people like coffee too much,
虽然一杯意式浓缩咖啡有很多积极的影响，但仍然可能会使用超标。
and while there are many positive effects to having that shot of espresso, you can go overboard.
不管你信不信，在极端情况下，有人死于过量摄入咖啡因。
In extreme cases, believe it or not, people have died from overdosing on caffeine.
在不太极端的情况下，人则会感觉有点神经质。
In less extreme cases people just feel wired.
早上来上一杯感觉可能还不错，但在夜间却可能成为一场噩梦。
That might not be so bad in the morning, but at nighttime it can be a nightmare.
你可以看看星巴克或其他咖啡店的含量介绍，看看一杯咖啡里含有多少咖啡因。
You can look at coffee charts from Starbucks or other outlets and see how much caffeine there is in one cup.
这取决于杯子的大小，在即时速溶咖啡中可能只有50毫克咖啡因，
It depends on the size of the cup, but your instant stuff might just have 50 mgs of caffeine in it
这并不会让你点燃一些电子音乐，然后开始跳舞。
which isn't going to make you fire up some techno music and start dancing.
但在许多咖啡店出售的咖啡中含有200毫克甚至400毫克的咖啡因。
But many outlets sell cups of coffee with 200 or even 400 mg of caffeine in the cup.
星巴克的黄金烘焙（Blonde Roast）咖啡中含有475毫克的巨量咖啡因。
The Starbucks Blonde Roast has a massive 475 mg of caffeine in it.
有专家说，当你摄入500到600毫克的咖啡因时，就像服用了小剂量的安非他命。
Some experts say when you get a hit of 500 to 600 mg it's like a small dose of amphetamine.
饮茶的人会表现得好一点，因为一杯普通的茶可能只含有50毫克的咖啡因，
Tea drinkers will fare better as a regular cup might only contain 50 mg of caffeine,
但是考虑到有些人喝茶就像上瘾了一样，同样也可能会产生“喝茶高潮”。
but given some folks drink tea as if they were addicted to it, it's possible to get a tea high.
总之，你真的不应该在晚上摄入咖啡因。
The long and short of all this is you really shouldn't be consuming caffeine in the evening at all.
我们建议你在午后喝上最后一杯。
We suggest you have your last hit in the afternoon.
我们发现的一项研究告诉我们，
We found one study that told us
睡前6小时摄入咖啡因会使人们的睡眠时间减少1小时。
that having caffeine 6 hours before bedtime reduced people's sleep time by one hour.
能量饮料也含有咖啡因，所以你在派对上喝的10瓶红牛伏特加
Energy drinks also contain caffeine, and so those 10 vodka Red Bulls you had at the party
不仅会让你表现得像个白痴，还可能会减少你的睡眠时间。
might not only just make you act like an idiot but will likely cut down your sleep time.
如果不是注明非咖啡因品种，那这罐可乐就会含有咖啡因，所以请记住
A can of Coke will have caffeine in it if it's not the non-caffeine variety, so remember
睡前喝些软饮料可能不是一件好事。
that some soft drinks before bed might not be a good thing.
美国食品药物管理局告诉我们，咖啡因在大多数情况下是种安全的物质，
The U.S. Food and Drug Administration tells us that caffeine is for the most part a safe substance,
但是也说你不应该在一天内摄入超过400毫克的咖啡因。
but it says you should probably not consume more than 400 mg a day.
现在的你成天喝着茶或者咖啡，就着可乐吃着中晚餐的时候，就很容易超标。
That's easy to do when your chugging tea and coffee all day and then having your Cokes for lunch and dinner.
那晚上吃东西有什么坏处吗？
What about eating late at night?
一些研究告诉我们，晚食者可能会体重增加，因为你在睡觉时基本不活动。
Some studies tell us that late eaters might gain weight because you're hardly active when you're sleeping.
宾夕法尼亚大学（University of Pennsylvania）在2017年进行的另一项研究称，
Another study conducted by the University of Pennsylvania in 2017 said
深夜进食会增加人们患2型糖尿病的几率。
eating late at night gives people a higher chance of getting type 2 diabetes.
研究称，晚上进食会提高胆固醇水平，
The study said late eating can raise cholesterol levels and so give you
因此也更容易患心脏病。
a better chance of having a heart attack.
事实上，并没有多少关于晚吃让人快乐的信息，但很多人都这样做。
In fact, there isn't much happy information concerning eating late, but lots of people do it.
想象一下，某个孩子一边嚼着立体脆(Doritos)薯片，一边喝着可口可乐，
Imagine this, some kid munching on a bag of Doritos while drinking a Coke and
一边在睡觉之前浏览着让人“嫉妒”的朋友圈动态。
scrolling through envy-inducing Facebook right before that kid wants to sleep.
这就好比有人去夜总会冥想
That makes about as much sense as someone going to a nightclub to meditate
或者去射击场准备微积分考试一样不符合逻辑。
or heading to the shooting range to study for their calculus exam.
根本没有任何意义，但是人们做到了。
It makes no sense at all, but people do it.
我们认为你们中的一些人现在正在做类似的事情，但你们可以稍后再承认。
We imagine a few of you are doing something like that right now, but you can admit to that later.
晚上让你的消化系统休息一下。
At nighttime give your digestive system a break.
有证据表明，饱腹的食物不仅对你的健康有害，
There is evidence that it's not only bad for your health,
而且也会影响你的睡眠质量。
but food in you full stomach can affect how much quality sleep you get.
如果你看了我们的另一个睡眠节目，你就会知道好的睡眠是
If you watched our other sleep show you'll know that the good kind of sleep is
当你进入到深睡眠，这被称为快速眼动周期。
when you go into deep sleep, and these are called rapid eye movement cycles.
一个晚上，你应该有大约5个这样的周期。
You should be getting about five of these a night.
另一种睡眠称为非快速眼动。
The other sleep is called non rapid eye movement.
研究表明睡前吃东西可以减少深睡眠周期，
Studies have shown that food before bed can reduce these deep sleep cycles
妨碍你去做那些对心理健康很重要的梦。
and prevent you from having those dreams that are so important to your mental well-being.
糖、碳水化合物和脂肪是晚上最不该吃的东西，
Sugar, carbs and fats are the worst things to eat late,
但也许我们会原谅你吃了一小口香蕉。
so perhaps we'll forgive you for having one small bit of banana.
这是我们发现的一篇文章的结论，“在睡觉时间吃东西，
This is the conclusion of one article we found, “Eating during bedtime hours,
无论是顿大餐还是在看你最喜欢的节目时吃的一点零食，
whether it's a large dinner or a small snack while watching your favorite TV show,
虽然看起来有助于入睡，但实际上可能会损害你的整体健康和新陈代谢，
while it may seem to help you fall asleep, may actually harm your overall health and metabolism,
在体内造成额外的压力。”
creating added stress inside the body.”
所以，这就是全部了。
So, there you go.
如果你身体健康，没有身体或精神疾病，
If you are healthy and not suffering from some physical or mental disease
这就可能是你睡眠不好的原因。
this might be the reason you are not sleeping well.
可遵循的建议也非常简单。
It's really simple advice to follow.
睡前两个小时关掉你的电子设备。
Just turn off your gadgets two hours before bed.
睡前至少六个小时不要摄入咖啡因，睡前也不要进食。
Don't consume caffeine at least six hours before bed and don't eat before you sleep.
如果你真的在半夜看这个节目，并且嘴里塞满了巧克力
If indeed you are watching this show at midnight with your mouth full of chocolate being cement-mixed
和可口可乐，那你基本上是在制造一场完美的糟糕睡眠。
with Coca-Cola you are basically creating a perfect storm of bad sleep.
还是说你不同意这些观点？
Or do you disagree?
在评论中告诉我们你的想法。
Tell us what you think in the comments.
另外，请务必查看我们的其他视频，“你知道的关于睡眠的一切都是错误的。”
Also, be sure to check out our other video Everything You Know About Sleep Is Wrong.
感谢你的收看，一如既往，不要忘记点赞，分享和订阅。
Thanks for watching, and as always, don't forget to like, share and subscribe.
下次见。
See you next time.